http://www.buypromosonline.com/termsandcondition.php

Factory holiday closures & shipping carriers holiday schedules may result in longer order times right now. If you have a firm in-hands date please contact us before ordering sales@bpopromos.com.
We're serious about service!
Shop for custom stress balls
704-291-3028
Menu
Search
Home
About
Customer Comments
FAQ
Terms & Conditions
Please read the following information carefully before submitting your order:
(1) Payment: For your security, we will only process your credit card order if the credit card you provide for payment matches the billing address on the order form. If the credit card information and address verification don't match, your order will not be processed.
(2) Rush service: Rush service is available on hundreds of items, but cannot be guaranteed. If you are requesting rush service the following parameters apply: (1) Catalog quantities only. (2) One color, one location imprint only for next-day rush. More than one color/location may be possible for a 3-day rush. If you are requesting a 3-day rush for more than one color/location we will advise whether this is possible after reviewing your order details. (3) No art proof will be provided for a 1 day rush and cannot be guaranteed for 3 day rush. (4) Artwork must be submitted in usable format (see production info tab on product page) and will be used as provided. We do not edit artwork for rush orders. (5) Based on the time of day you submit your order, we will ship on 1 day rush: either the following or 2 business days from order date; 3 day rush: either 3 or 4 business days after order date. If rush service is not possible a customer service representative will contact you.
(3) PMS Color Match:If you require a PMS color match an additional charge may apply. This charge can be found on the Item Details tab. Please note your PMS color(s) in the special instructions box.
(4) Art proofs: An emailed art proof is offered with standard service orders and most 3-day rush orders. No art proof is available for next day rush orders.
(5) Total order cost: The sub-total shown below is not complete. Additional decorating, rush or shipping charges may appear on the order acknowledgement you will receive shortly after our customer service team has reviewed your order details.
(6) Over/Under Run Policy: Every effort will be made to ship the exact quantity order. However, Our suppliers reserve the right to allow a possible 5% variance over/under the quantity you have ordered for quality control purposes. You will be billed for the quantity shipped.
(7) Order Cancellation: Once your order has gone to production you will be responsible for payment of the order.
(8) Important Shipping Information: If you noted an in-hands date on your order, we will make every effort to meet your deadline. In some cases a rush charge may apply. Once your order is picked up by UPS or Fed Ex it is their responsibility to deliver on time. We base the estimated ship date on transit times provided by these carriers. Severe weather may cause delays. We ship our orders with no signature required. However, UPS and Fed Ex reserve the right to not leave a package or may require delivery signature at either a business or residential address at the delivery driver’s discretion. UPS and Fed Ex define the end of a business day as a delivery time up to 7:30 PM. A residential address is defined as a location that is a home, including a business operating out of a home. Buy Promos, LLC cannot guarantee delivery dates.
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for BuyPromosOnline.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information  You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security  We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 704-291-3028 or via email at sales@bpopromos.com.
Shop for custom stress balls
Business Hours: Monday-Friday, 9AM - 5PM EST, United States
Copyright © 2013-2020 Buy Promos, LLC. All rights reserved. Terms and Conditions | Sitemap
Website Design by Burgeon Software LLC.
